Guide to the Dept. of Biometrics records,1948-2006.
Dept. of Biometrics records,1948-2006.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dept. of Biometrics records, 1948-2006.
21/40/3204
Cornell University.Dept. of Biometrics.
24 cubic ft.
Research Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Annual reports, correspondence, budgets, course lectures, syllabi, labs, exams, and problem sets of the Dept. of Biometrics, New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, Cornell University.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
In 1966, the status of the Biometrics Unit was recognized in the renamed Dept. of Plant Breeding and Biometry. In 1998, the unit became the Dept. of Biometrics, affiliated with the Dept. of Statistical Science. As of 2002, it was the Dept. of Biological Statistics and Computational Biology.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Annual reports of the Dept. of Biometrics, New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences, Cornell University.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University.Biometrics Unit.; Cornell University.Dept. of Biological Statistics and Computational Biology.
Subjects:
Biometry--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Annual Reports
  - July 1, 1948-June 30, 2001 (Box 1)
- Abstracts, correspondence, committee reports, other papers, budget reports, project reports, course information: notes, lectures, exams, problem sets, lab reports
  - 1948-1962 (Box 2)
  - 1962-1966 (Box 3)
  - 1966-1969 (Box 4)
  - 1969-1972 (Box 5)
  - 1972-1975 (Box 6)
  - 1975-1976 (Box 7)
  - 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - 1978-1981 (Box 9)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 10)
  - 1984-1987 (Box 11)
  - 1983-1988 (Box 12)
  - 1988-1989 (Box 13)
  - 1990-1992 (Box 14)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 15)
  - 1994-1995 (Box 16)
  - 1980-1996 (Box 17)
  - 1996-1997 (Box 18)
  - 1997-1998 (Box 19)
  - 1998-1999 (Box 20)
  - 1999-2000 (Box 21)
  - 2000-2002 (Box 22)
  - 2002-2006 (Box 23)
- Exam questions, course syllabi
  - 1969-2003 (Box 24)